Abduqodirov Sarvar

Software Engineer .Net & Angular

+998 93 234 03 16

abduqodirovsarvar.2002@gmail.com

Tashkent, Uzbekistan

https://www.linkedin.com/in/abduqodirov-sarvarbek

https://github.com/AbdugodirovSarvar

Profile

Skilled and curious young software engineer with 1.5 years of experience in building robust systems using .NET Core on backend and Angular, TypeScript, JavaScript on frontend. Wants to design solid architecture and clean code. Good understanding of object oriented programming and fast learning.

Professional Experience

Full-Stack Software Engineer at Olmatech LLC (part-time)

Tashkent, 06/2024 - present

- Development of web applications and systems, support for these applications.
- Asp.Net core, EF core, SQL, JS, Bootstrap, Angular, TypeScript, Docker, Windows Server, IIS, SSL

Software Engineer at Bepro-DEVHUB (part-time)

Tashkent, 02/2024 - 12/2024

- Development of web applications and systems, support for these applications.
- Asp.Net core, EF core, SQL, JS, Angular, TypeScript, xUnit, Git, Docker

Freelancer as a Software Engineer

Tashkent, 06/2023 - 01/2024

- Development and deployment of web applications. Created some websites, telegram bots, CRM sytems for some companies and others.
- Asp.Net core, SQL, EF core, JS, xUnit, Git, Redis, Docker, IIS, SSL, Telegram-Bot-Api

Itransition Software Development Company, Internship

Tashkent, 03/2023 - 06/2023

- Development of web applications and work with a team. Created some programs with .Net, JavaScript, React, NodeJs and wrote registration and authorization web applications with n-tier and Clean Architecture in Asp.Net.
- C#, Asp.Net core, SQL, EF, JS, Html & Css, React, xUnit, Moq, Git, Redis

Online Courses & Certifications

- Building Services with ASP.NET Web API Coursera
- Object Oriented Development using C# Coursera
- Programming in C#: A comprehensive approach to C# Fundamental Coursera
- Open Source Software Development Methods <u>Coursera</u>
- Introduction to Cyber security Tools & Cyber Attacks Coursera

Education

• Tashkent University of Information Technology, bachelor Information Security, Cyber Security, Complex Protection of IT Objects Tashkent, 2020 - 2024

Najot Ta'lim digital academy, Course
.Net-bootcamp result, Asp.Net backend developer

Tashkent, 07/2022 - 04/2023

Skills

Asp.Net core, EF core, CQRS, Message Brokers, Cache, Git, Git Actions, SQL, NoSQL, Unit Testing, Angular, TypeScript, JavaScript, SOLID, DRY, Design Patterns, Docker, nginx, IIS, Linux, SSL

Languages

Uzbek [Native]

• English [B2] - Learning

Russian [B1] - Learning